Guide to the Committee to Protect Journalists Rcords,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Committee to Protect Journalists Records,
1978-2008
Committee to Protect Journalists
213.5 linear ft. (170 record storage cartons and 1 video box)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library New York, NY. 10027
HR#0010
7745809
The records of the Committee to Protect Journalists (CPJ) document the organization's work in promoting press freedom around the world and include clippings, correspondence, minutes, planning materials, publications, and research materials.
Historical Note
The Committee to Protect Journalists (CPJ) was founded at a time when violence against journalists was escalating, particularly in Latin America. A particular case, involving Alcibiades Gonzalez Delvalle, inspired the founding of CPJ. In 1980, Gonzalez, a prominent Paraguayan newspaper columnist, was touring in the United States when he was informed that a warrant for his arrest had been issued in Asuncion, and his case was publicized prior to his return to Paraguay. The case continued to receive media attention upon Gonzalez's arrest, and the resulting pressure on the Paraguayan government led to his release. But in working on this case, journalists who had helped Gonzalez in the United States also realized that there was no organization of American journalists dedicated to assisting their colleagues working in foreign countries. This group approached other reporters, columnists, and editors who had demonstrated an interest in freedom of the press. The most prominent of these was Walter Cronkite, who agreed to serve as the honorary chairman for the newly formed CPJ.
CPJ has grown tremendously since its founding in 1981. Its work has expanded to deal not only with freeing imprisoned journalists, but also working for their safety, and arranging safe conduct for those in immediate danger. The CPJ continues to work for freedom for journalists, the press, and other media outlets by documenting, publicizing, and protesting abuses of the press around the world.
Scope and Content
The records of the Committee to Protect Journalists (CPJ) primarily document the Board of Directors, the International Press Freedom Awards Dinner, coverage of CPJ in the press, and actions, cases, programs, research, and publications related to the organization's work in documenting press conditions and promoting press freedom in individual countries and regions.
The coverage of the collection extends through 2008, but is most comprehensive through the early 2000s for most series of records at this time.
The Board of Directors' records include correspondence (1980-1994) and materials related to board meetings and minutes (1981-1995), as well as Executive Committee (1989-1997) and other committee records (1990, 1995-1997). The Board of Directors' records also include the organization's articles of incorporations and several versions of its bylaws. Records such as members' biographies and members' lists are included in this series, but are incomplete. The collection does not currently include any board records for 1998-present.
The International Press Freedom Awards Dinner (IPFAD), which was started in 1991, is well-documented in the collection, particular for 1994-1999. The files include information on the awardees, event planning, and press coverage of the event. The coverage of other CPJ events is less comprehensive; most of these files can be found in Series IV: CPJ Office Files.
The collection also contains good documentation of the press' coverage of CPJ. CPJ kept clippings of instances where CPJ's work was discussed in the press or where CPJ was cited as a source of information, and used a clippings service to assist in this documentation effort. The collection contains both chronological and topical clippings for 1981-2008.
The collection's largest portion of records deals with actions, cases, programs, research, and publications related to the organization's work in documenting press conditions and promoting press freedom in individual countries and regions. There is a separate series of that documents only country actions and protest letters in Series V. The majority of the other records related to this work are filed in Series VI. Much of the documentation is Series VI consists of records related to CPJ's data-gathering activities, conducted for the purpose of investigating and documenting cases and press conditions. Many of these records consist of research materials gathered from secondary sources. Other records - correspondence, documentation of telephone calls, press releases, protest letters, etc. - tend to be mixed in with the research materials in the same files. CPJ publications that document CPJ's activities and press conditions in particular countries are filed in Series VII: Publications.
Series VII: Publications contains published newsletters, serial publications, reports, and other publications issued by CPJ. The collection's coverage of these publications is best before the mid-1990s, when CPJ began to regularly distribute publications and reports through its website.
There is a lack of certain types of records in the collection which would provide more comprehensive documentation of the organization as a whole. In particular, there is a lack of Executive Directors' records, financial records, membership records, policy documents, and press releases in the collection.
There are few records from Executive Directors, and a small set of records related to William Orne is incomplete and was probably created and maintained by secretarial staff. There are no complete and identifiable sets of records kept by Executive Directors currently present in the collection.
The collection includes a small amount of CPJ policy documents, procedural manuals, and informational materials outside of the Board of Directors records. Materials of this type were gathered together and placed in Series IV: CPJ Office Files. There are additional materials of this type found with Alice Chasan's files that were kept with her materials in Series VIII.1.
The collection also lacks financial records, including annual financial statements, budgets, and tax documents. There are no annual reports in the collection. Existing financial records are included in Series IV: CPJ Office Files. These primarily include records from 1981-1984, although there are a few records from the mid-1990s. There are records related to development efforts and grants in Series IX: Development, but they are incomplete.
There are few membership records in the collection; these are also filed in Series IV: CPJ Office Files. The few existing files date from 1989-1990 and 1999-2000.
The documentation of activities related to communications and publicity is incomplete and the coverage is uneven. The majority of existing files date from the 1990s. Most problematic is the lack of a single series of press releases; these are scattered in files related to country and program work, events, and publicity throughout the collection.
There is also little audiovisual material in the records. This is primarily because CPJ does not produce much of its own audiovisual material, and instead obtains material from news organizations such as the Associated Press for many of its publications. The collection does have some audiovisual material, particularly photographs, filed in Series VI, VIII, and XI.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in twelve series and several subseries.
Series I. Board of Directors, 1981-1997
Series II. Chronological Files, 1984-1994 November
Series III. Clippings Files, 1981-2008
Subseries III.1. CPJ In the News, 1996 December-2006
Subseries III.2. Chronological Clippings, 1981-2008
Subseries III.3. Topical Clippings, 1981-2008
Series IV. CPJ Office Files, 1978-2005
Series V. Country Actions and Protest Letters, 1978-1999
Subseries V.1. Alphabetical by Country, 1978-1997
Subseries V.2. Chronological, 1992-1999
Series VI. Country & Regional Program & Research Files, 1981-2007
Subseries VI.1. General, 1990-2001
Subseries VI.2. Africa, 1981-2007
Subseries VI.3. Americas, 1979-2004
Subseries VI.4. Asia, 1981-2006
Subseries VI.5. Europe and Central Asia, 1981-2005
Subseries VI.6. Middle East and North Africa, 1981-2007
Series VII. Publications, 1982-2008
Subseries VII.1. Newsletters and Serial Publications, 1982-2007
Subseries VII.2. Reports and Other Publications, 1983-1999, 2008
Series VIII. Communications & Publicity, 1981-2007
Subseries VIII.1. Alice Chasan Files, 1990-1999 [Bulk Dates: 1995-1999]
Subseries VIII.1.1. CPJ Board of Directors Materials, 1996-1999
Subseries VIII.1.2. CPJ Committees and Other Files, 1995-1999
Subseries VIII.1.3. Subject Files, 1990-1999
Subseries VIII.2. Judy Clark Files, 1999-2001
Subseries VIII.3. Subject Files, 1982-2007
Series IX. Development, 1981-2001
Subseries IX.1. General, 1982-1988
Subseries IX.2. Foundations and Others, 1981-1995
Subseries IX.3. Grants, 1992-2001
Series X. International Press Freedom Awards Dinner, 1991-2007, Undated
Series XI. Audiovisual Records and Computer Disks, 1980s-2001, Undated
Subseries XI.1. Photographs, 1980-2000, Undated
Subseries XI.2. Videotapes, 1995-1997, Undated
Subseries XI.3. Computer Disks and Audio Cassettes, circa 1990s
Series XII. Organization Files, 1978-2002
Subjects
Committee to Protect Journalists; Censorship; Freedom of the Press; Government and the Press; Human Rights advocacy; Journalism--Political aspects; Journalists--Crimes against; Journalists--Death; Journalists--Protection; Journalists--Violence against; Press and politics; Press law
Access Restrictions
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions, except that access to Box 171 is temporarily restricted while the contents of the box receive conservation treatment.
Acquisition
Committee to Protect Journalists Deposit. April 2010 2009-2010-M106
Committee to Protect Journalists Deposit April 2010 2009-2010-M110
Committee to Protect Journalists Deposit September 2010 2010-2011-M018
Committee to Protect Journalists Deposit March 2012 2011-2012-M085
Finding aid in repository and online; folder level control.
- Series I: Board of Directors, 1981-1997
  This series includes board and committee meeting minutes and related materials, correspondence, lists of board members, subject files, and files related to individual board members. The files include CPJ’s articles of incorporation and several versions of its bylaws.
  - General
    - General Information, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      (Includes By-laws)
    - Additions to By-laws (various), 1994,Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lists of Members
    - Board Lists, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors & Board Classes, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors/Executive Committee, 1992 (Includes biographies for nominees) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Board Members, 1990-1994 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      (In CPJ Reference Information)
    - CPJ Board of Directors, 1997 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      (List of Members)
  - Member Biographies
    - Board Bios, circa 1988-1994 (2 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Friedman, Joshua, circa 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Moses, Judith, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Nelson, Anne, circa 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board Meeting Minutes/Information
    - 1981-1990 (4 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 12 to 15)
    - 1988 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1989 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1990
      - March 16 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - November 15 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1991 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1992
      - April 30 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - November 19 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1993
      - Board List and Meeting Schedule (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - May 20 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - November 19 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1994
      - May 19 (3 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 26 to 28)
      - November 17 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1995
      - May 25 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - November 30 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board Correspondence
    - General
      - 1980-1989 (10 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 32 to 41)
      - 1990-1991 (4 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 1993-1994 (2 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 5 to 6)
    - Individual Members
      (Individual files contain general information and are very small in size, with the exception of the file for Kati Marton)
      - Alina, Frank, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Anderson, Terry, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Brokaw, Tom, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Cronkite, Walter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - del Olmo, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Friedman, Josh, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Goodale, James C., 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Graham, Katherine, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Ibarguen, Alberto, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Kovach, Bill, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Kramer, James, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Lewis, Anthony, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - MacArthur, John A., 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Marton, Kati, 1994-1997 (4 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 20 to 23)
        (Includes background materials)
      - Massing, Michael, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Moses, Judth, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Oakes, John B., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Rather, Dan, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Roberts, Gene, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Seigenthaler, John, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Shaw, Bernard, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee Meetings
    - 1989-1990 (3 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 31 to 33)
    - 1990
      - August 16 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - September 7 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - September 13 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - October 25 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - December 13 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1991
      - January 17 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - February 21 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - March 21 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - April 18 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - June 20 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - July 18 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - September 19 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - November 21 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - December 19 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 1992
      - March 19 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - April 16 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - May 21 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - June 18 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - July 16 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - August (Memo Only, No Meeting) (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - September 17 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - November 17 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - December 17 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 1993
      - January 21 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - February 17 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - March 18 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - April 13 (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - October 26 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      - December 16 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - 1994
      - January 20 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - February 17 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - March 17 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - April 21 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - June 16 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - July 21 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - September 22 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - October 24 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - December 15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1995
      - January 26 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - March 30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - July 27 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - September 28 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1996 December 17 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1997 January 30 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Subcommittees
    - Development Committee, 1990 (3 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 15 to 17)
    - Governance Subcommittee, 1995-1996 (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 18 to 19)
    - Priorities Subcommittee, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 21 to 22)
  - Subject Files
    - Budgets, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - By-Laws & Board Travel Policy (PEN, HRW, Lawyers Committee), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - International Advisory Board, 1990-1992 (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 25 to 26)
    - Management Review
      - Management Review and Memo, 1995 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Management Assistance Group (MAG), 1995-1997 (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 28 to 29)
      - Management Review (LO), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Board Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Series II: Chronological Files, 1984 November-1994
  This series contains chronological correspondence files for the organization.
  - 1984 November-1985 July (9 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 32 to 40)
  - 1985 August-1987 February (19 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 1 to 19)
  - 1987 March-September (7 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 1 to 7)
  - 1987 November (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1990 January-June (6 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 9 to 14)
  - 1990 July-December (11 Folders) (Box 6, Folder 1 to 11)
  - 1991 January-August (9 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 1 to 9)
  - 1991 September-December (6 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 1 to 6)
  - 1992 January-May (5 Folders) (Box 171, Folder 1 to 5)
    (Access to Box 171 is temporarily restricted while the contents of the Box receive conservation treatment.)
  - 1993 January-March (4 Folders) (Box 171, Folder 6 to 9)
  - March Chrono II, 1993 March (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - 1993 April-1994 March (19 Folders) (Box 156, Folder 5 to 23)
  - 1994 April-December (18 Folders) (Box 157, Folder 1 to 18)
- Series III: Clippings Files, 1981-2008
  CPJ kept clippings files of stories that either mentioned the CPJ’s work or cited CPJ as a source. CPJ used a clipping service to help document this news coverage.
  - Subseries III.1: CPJ in the News, 1996 December-2006 June
    CPJ created, photocopied, and distributed sets of clippings via a quasi-publication called CPJ in the News. These sets are filed chronologically; if specific topics were noted on the cover page of the set, the topics are noted in the container list.
    - 1996 December (Box 168, Folder 9)
      (CPJ’s Kati Marton Goes to Belgrade to Support Struggle for Press Freedom)
    - 1997 January 24 (Box 168, Folder 10)
      (Recent Clippings December 15th-January 24th)
    - 1997 March 25 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      (Attacks on the Press in 1996)
    - 1997 April 30 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - 1997 June 4 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      (Daoud Kuttab; 1997 Enemies of the Press; News from the Regions)
    - 1997 June 25 (Box 168, Folder 14)
      (Daoud Kuttab; Dangers for journalists in Mexico, Columbia, and Cambodia)
    - 1997 June-October (Box 168, Folder 15)
      (Violence and Law Suits Plague Journalists in Mexico)
    - 1997 July (Box 168, Folder 16)
      (Turkey Campaign)
    - 1997 July-August (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - 1997 September 24 (Box 168, Folder 18)
      (Hong Kong Report; 1997 CPJ Awards; Coverage of Press Crackdowns in the Middle East and Eastern Europe; Attacks on the press in the Americas)
    - 1997 September-November (Box 168, Folder 19)
      (Hong Kong; China)
    - 1997 November 13 (Box 168, Folder 20)
      (International Press Freedom Awards)
    - 1997 December 15 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - 1997 December 19 (Box 168, Folder 22)
      (CPJ’s Marton to Press Leaders in Bosnia, Yugoslavia for Independent Media Guarantees)
    - 1997 September-1998 February (Box 168, Folder 23)
      (CPJ’s New Efforst to Free Turkish Journalists; 26 Journalists Murdered in 1997 US Reporter Jailed in South Korea; Nigeria’s Crackdown on Dissent; and other news.)
    - 1997 September-1998 March (Box 168, Folder 24)
      (The Americas: Mexico, Cuba, and other news)
    - 1998 March (Box 168, Folder 25)
      (Attacks on the Press 1997)
    - 1998 April-May (Box 168, Folder 26)
      (Regional and home news)
    - 1998 May (Box 168, Folder 27)
      (‘Enemies of the Press’ - World Press Freedom Day Newsmakers)
    - 1998 May-June (Box 168, Folder 28)
      (CPJ Names New Director; Nigeria; Regional News)
    - 1998 July (Box 168, Folder 29)
    - 1998 October 19 (Box 168, Folder 30)
    - 1998 Fall (Box 168, Folder 31)
    - 1998 December 17 (Box 168, Folder 32)
    - 1998 December-1999 March (Box 168, Folder 33)
    - 1999 Spring (Box 168, Folder 34)
      (Attacks on the Press 1998)
    - 1999 March-May 6 (Box 168, Folder 35)
    - 2000 January (Box 168, Folder 36)
    - 2000 August-September (Box 168, Folder 37)
    - 2001 Fall (Box 168, Folder 38)
      (Press Advocacy Group Demands Release of French Reporter; CPJ Asks Taliban to Free British Journalist; Journalists Protest Censoring of Coverage; US-Based Press Freedom Group Protests Plaestinian Authority’s Confiscation of Footage; New Tactic of Terrorists is to Attack the Media; Jiang Weiping; Jiang Zemin)
    - CPJ Media Clips, 2003 August-2004 February (Box 168, Folder 39)
    - 2005 January-July (Box 168, Folder 40)
    - 2005 October-2006 February (Box 168, Folder 41)
      (Awards Dinner; Imprisoned List; Iraq; China; Mexico; Attacks on the Press release; Regional News)
    - 2006 March-June (Box 168, Folder 42)
      (Most Censored List; Staff Op Eds; Jill Carroll’s Release; Journalists Killed in Iraq; China; Saudi Arabia; Columbia; Ethiopia)
  - Subseries III.2: Chronological Clippings, 1981-2008
    This subseries contains clippings files that are arranged chronologically.
    - 1981-1986 (5 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 15 to 19)
    - Clips on CPJ (Copies), 1988 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - 1988-1991 (10 Folders) (Box 157, Folder 19 to 28)
    - 1990 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - 1993-1997 February (19 Folders) (Box 157, Folder 29 to 47)
    - CPJ List of Foreign Press Clips on CPJ, circa 1994 (Box 152, Folder 59)
    - 1999 Fall (Box 159, Folder 30)
    - 2000 (3 Folders) (Box 159, Folder 32 to 34)
    - 2001 February (Box 159, Folder 41)
    - 2001 June-2002 April (11 Folders) (Box 159, Folder 42 to 52)
    - 2001 November-December (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - 2002 May-July (4 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 1 to 4)
    - 2003 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - 2005 Fall (2 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 10 to 11)
    - 2006 (15 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 19 to 33)
    - 2007 (3 Folders) (Box 160, Folder 50 to 52)
    - 2008 (Box 160, Folder 54)
  - Subseries III.3: Topical Clippings, 1981-2008
    This subseries contains clippings files that are arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - Attacks on the Press
      - 1988 Report
        - Press Coverage, 1989 (3 Folders) (Box 157, Folder 48 to 50)
        - Press Release--Originals, 1989 (Box 157, Folder 51)
      - 1989 Report--Press Coverage, 1990 (2 Folders) (Box 158, Folder 1 to 2)
      - 1990 Report--Press Coverage, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - 1991 Report
        - Press Coverage, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 4)
        - Incorrect AP Stories, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - 1992 Report--Press Coverage, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - 1993 Report--Press Coverage, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - Report, 1996 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - 2001 Report, 2002 March (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Board and Staff--Articles and Clippings
      - 1984-1990 September (2 Folders) (Box 158, Folder 10 to 11)
      - 1990 October-1994 (6 Folders) (Box 158, Folder 12 to 17)
    - Board Members, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Bustios, Hugo. Case Coverage, 1990 (Box 158, Folder 18)
      (Peru)
    - Cartoonists and Freedom of Speech Stats from Around the World (Box 160, Folder 34)
    - CPJ
      - CPJ-Protests, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Statement Re: CPJ, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Chile--Clippings About, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Cuba
      - Coverage CPJ Cuba, 2008 March (Box 160, Folder 55)
    - De Dios Unanue, Manuel. Press, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - Domestic Clips, 1990-1994 (5 Folders) (Box 158, Folder 21 to 25)
    - Enemies of the Press, 1996 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Clips, 1990 March-1994 (5 Folders) (Box 158, Folder 26 to 30)
    - Guerin, Veronica--Clippings with CPJ Citations, 1996 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - International News, 2003 (3 Folders) (Box 106, Folder 9 to 11)
    - International Press, 1995 (Box 126, Folder 16)